CORENTIN MATHIEU

IT STUDENT

INFO

ADDRESS

28 ROUTE DE MACLAMOD, CHAVANOD, 74650, France

PHONE

0686007771

EMAIL

Cocod.tv@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH

Apr, 7, 2000

NATIONALITY

French

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

• • • •

PHP

• • • •

C# .NET

.

JS/JQuery

• • • • 0

SOL

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

LANGUAGES

French (first language)

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet

Spanish

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

English

• • • • 0

HOBBIES

- New technologies and high tech in globality
- Multimedia : photos/videos montage
- Sport : English Boxing at Montblanc Boxing Club 74

JOB OBJECTIVE

Front developer

I am a second-year university student in computer science and I would like to enhance my capabilities in this field with a strong experience in a software company. As an excellent programmer, I can provide your company with he best up-to-date programming language. Designing efficient and user-friendly applications is at the heart of my skills, and this makes me a multi-task developer.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Histoire d'or, Sales assistant

Epagny, France

Dec 2018 — Dec 2019

To advice the client about the products and operate the sales.

Ecotel, Data updating

Cran-Gevrier, France

Jul 2019 — Jul 2019

Summer job: Updating all the data of clients and products. (Using ERP Divalto, Excel and SQL language)

Tessier technique, Teissier technique

Chavanod, France

Jul 2016 — Jul 2018

Summer job: Working as an Operator/Conductor with a more responsibilities every year.

EDUCATION

DUT Info, IUT - University of Savoy

Annecy, France

Sep 2018 — Jul 2020

French two-year technical university degree in computer science (similar to an Associate's degree).

Degree loading...

French Technological Baccalaureate, Lycée Louis Lachenal

Argonay, France

Dec 2019 — Dec 2019

High school diploma: with high honors

Languege

Dec 2019 — Dec 2019

REFERENCES

Stephanie Bouchon from IUT Annecy

stephanie.bouchon@univ-smb.fr | English Teacher

Pascal Colin from IUT Annecy

 $\verb|pascal.colin@univ-smb.fr| UML, Agile Software Development and Database teacher|$